Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials series, 1965-2009 and undated; 1
  - Acapella Stella (Maddy Prier), undated; 515
    - Original audiocassette (Box 122, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0461)
  - Janis Ian / Hunger, 1997; 516
    - Original audiocassette (Box 122, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0462)
  - Sue Fink / True Life Adventure, 1989; 517
    - Original audiocassette (Box 122, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0463)
  - Ranch Romance / Blue Blazes, 1991; 518
    - Original audiocassette (Box 122, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0464)
  - Rachel Bagby / Reach Across the Lines, 1989; 519
    - Original audiocassette (Box 122, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0465)
  - Rose Polenzani / Anybody, 1999; 520
    - Original audiocassette (Box 122, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0466)
  - Tiddas / Sing About Life, 1995; 521
    - Original audiocassette (Box 122, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0467)
  - Ladyslipper interview, undated; 522
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0468)
  - Assar Santana Chamel No. 6 Michiga W.M.I., undated; 523
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0469)
  - Fluke new songs, 1992; 524
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0470)
  - Margie Adam / Here is a Love Song, 1983; 525
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0471)
  - Opalanga / She-Roes Living Her-Story, 1990; 526
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0472)
  - Outloud Radio 11/26/96 first half, 1996; 527
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0473)
  - Outloud Radio 11/26/96 second half, 1996; 528
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0474)
  - Helen M. Luke / Old Age: Journey into Simplicity, 1992; 529
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0475)
  - Singer in the Storm: The Life and Music of Holly Near, 1991; 530
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0476)
  - Nancy Hopps / Relaxation Gift Set, 1994; 531
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0477)
  - Kathy Fire / Songs of Fire: Songs of a Lesbian Anarchist, 1993; 532
    - Original audiocassette (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL10140-CS-0478)